Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone.
We'll go where we all wanna go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
You heard him, didn't you?
Let's keep up the fight!
You really believe Straw
Hat will defeat me?
You really believe that
Wano's borders will open?
Just a fairy tale ending.
You're nothing but a damn child!
There's no way I'm losing!
I will defeat Kaido!
Our samurai are strong!
We're not waiting for Luffy!
We're facing you head on!
We're...
Good luck.
You're not alone.
I'll die beside you if I must.
Fripe Fripe Jutsu!
Grr.
Robot, Robot.
Momonosuke is out!
They're finished.
The samurai don't have a leader
anymore if that Brad's dead.
We gotta broadcast his
death to the whole island.
They'll surrender, of course, of course.
They've got nothing left.
Oh, that's a great idea!
Let's crush their spirits!
She's alive!
The crow is coming back!
Let's make our way to the performance
floor just like we planned.
Sound good? Uh-huh.
If Loopy is doing his best,
then we will as well. Agreed.
I'm so happy for Straw Hat.
Huh?
Is my Climatac talking to me?
Hello, Nami. No way.
It has a face too?
This is weird! Jeepers!
It's so cute!
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ha!
You really think Straw
Hat could defeat Kaido?
Are you stupid, or is this some joke?
I was just hoping I'd have the
pleasure of killing him myself.
But it's fine.
As long as he's dead, at least
he won't be a thorn in my side.
Speaking as someone who's
worked with him for a while,
I have a feeling he'll survive, even
if it doesn't make any damn sense.
Who asked you?
This is my fight.
Big mom's the enemy here.
Our enemy, so grow up!
This once we can form an alliance.
Maybe I'm such a genius that my
genius even surpassed myself.
Huh, I made that thing.
So if it can talk, it must be my
doing. What? No! Look, it's me!
You're all buzzers!
Last I saw, that other cloud ate you!
How the heck did you end up like this?
That was weird.
After Mama grabbed me, my
spirit started leaving my body.
Finish him off, Hera!
I was lost in a daze. Powerless.
And that Lady Hera was gonna couple me up!
I'll give you a snack out of pity.
Eat them and run, okay, girl?
Hurry!
Then you stretched out your
weapon and offered me a snack.
Eat them! Come on!
Wake up!
Here I go!
It's dinner time for more.
Anyhow, I guess when Hera bit me, it
smushed my body into your rod thingy.
And just like magic...
I came back to life, good as new.
Well, that's fine for you, but
it's a pain in the butt for me.
Oh, wait.
Even though you saved me,
you haven't forgiven me yet?
I don't have so much power anymore.
If you could just find
it in your heart, too.
Hold on, hold on.
Oh, hey.
That looks like the stage.
Tama, let's go there and give a command.
Right.
You listening, Onigashima?
I've got news!
The enemy's leader, Momo!
I'm sorry to interrupt, ma
'am, but the Sawhats are here!
It's a Huang lat!
Huang motor!
Listen!
I get it now.
This brat is the real problem! Tama!
Because of her, our gifters started
betraying each other one after the other.
She even got Big Mom on her side. No way.
She took that attack from Big
Mom and got right back up?
Papa got beat up because of you.
I thought I told you to leave her alone.
What?
I've never seen it do that before.
Mommy, just use your
baton like you always do.
I'll add attacks of my own.
Your skin's too tough
for us to break through.
Instead, we'll damage our
insides like Mama's attack did.
One good lightning blast
should do the trick.
No, that'll cause too much destruction.
We have to keep Otama sick.
What, Capote?
You got this, pal?
They're so dead!
Special attack, green star!
Sir Koza!
I separated them! Let me go!
I'm on it!
I thought Luffy's defeat
would shut the samurai down,
but not a single one of them surrendered.
Allow me to brief you on the situation.
A total of 5,000 troops on both sides
have been rendered unfit for combat.
When the battle began,
the Beast Pirates had 24,000
fighters, and the Rebels had 3,000.
However,
all of the pleasures and
waiters on the performance
floor seem to have turned
against Master Queen.
So the enemy gained 4,000 recruits.
At present, the Beast Pirates
have roughly 20,000 troops,
and the Rebels have roughly 7,000.
I didn't expect to see the gap
begin to close so late in the game.
The situation is completely volatile.
On that note, we just received a report
that might cause another shift in balance.
It's the Gifters!
They came here to kill us!
You're so screwed!
Pack it up, you traitors!
The gifters are here!
So the pleasures and waiters on this
floor revolted against Master Queen?
What, do they have a death wish?
Yeah, not very smart, are they?
Don't they get it?
Those peons are supposed to be
sacrificed at times like this.
Trash has no right to complain
about being taken out.
Wipe out every traitor on the floor!
Show no mercy!
Ah!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
Suck on that!
Rutheran Zeus!
Thundercloud, you're up!
Hello?
Zeus, you're out!
Huh?
I don't know if I'd call
me Zeus anymore. Huh?
I'm a cool new me after all, So why
don't you give me a cool new name?
Uh...
What is it?
Tell me, tell me!
Okay! Yes?
You're Fluff!
I'll stick with Zeus!
If you want to get to Nami,
you gotta go through me!
Give it your best shot!
I'm so sick of you!
Yeah? Same.
We've been playing tag for long enough.
I'm putting an end to this right now!
Lightning!
Oh no!
It's over.
No, it's not!
It's my job to hit my target!
And that's what I'm gonna do!
I can't believe this!
That means I need help you!
And what Paige might already do?
They've managed to take out
two of them as a dummy so slow!
What?
You're kidding me?
Are these guys a lot
stronger than we thought?
We're not actually losing, are we?
No, it can't be!
Calm down, Mace.
Everyone on Onigashima
can hear you freaking out!
Oh, shoot!
I forgot I was still broadcasting!
Ah!
Um, did I say they beat Lady Oji?
I meant Baby Robin Oji!
So she works as a transmitter, huh?
All right, then. Oof!
Special Attack Green Star Devil!
Ah!
Hey, Tama!
I don't know how her power works,
but that girl is like a transmitter.
If you make a command, the
whole island will hear you.
Go for it!
This is Otama!
Is that a kid?
Otama is here?
What's she doing?
It's not safe for her here. It's her!
Go get her, Master!
One more round!
One more kiss!
It's beautiful, isn't it, Otokon?
The fire festival is our time
to honor those we've lost.
We build a fire to reach
them in heaven itself.
I wonder if Daddy can see it.
Yes, of course he can.
There isn't a cloud in the sky, after all.
I'm sure he's watching
over you and watching
over the fate of this
country he loved so well.
You heard a voice?
Someone's there what?
You're right I see something.
Wait a sec!
Is that Straw Hat?
How the hell did you hear him underwater?
Who cares? Just bring him in!
Hurry!
He might be alive!
Whose baby is that?
Get out of here, you little shit!
This is a battlefield!
And what the hell did you do to Bao Huang?
Answer me!
Utama!
Hang in there!
You got this!
Ah!
Aren't you gonna complain
about being outnumbered?
Seems pretty unfair.
It was 5,000 versus
30,000 when we came here.
This is what everyone expected
from the very beginning.
A one-on-one battle was
never in the cards for me.
How annoyingly pragmatic of you.
This is no fun.
Our job is to keep the top
officers busy till Luffy wins.
So grumble as long as you like.
It's one after another with these guys.
A knock him down and more show up.
Strength and determination mean nothing.
You know what matters in this game.
Because this isn't a battle.
It's an Alto war.
It's your own fault for forgetting that.
What the hell is she still doing up there?
Just looking at her pisses me off!
Hey, someone take care of that brat!
Right, on it, sir!
Let's go! Yeah!
Otama, hurry! Do it now!
Hey, all my friends, you hate giving Tang!
I need to ask you a favor!
Can you switch sides, please?
Big bro, Lumi, and Mama Natsuka need you!
You've got to have some fun!
Let's all work together!
And turn down Carter!
The hell was that?
You think they'll listen to you just
because you ass nice, you dumb brat?
You're gonna pay for
putting it on my show!
Roger that, Master!
Your wish is my command!
Take down Tidal!
Now, let's start with you!
Get off of me!
What the hell is wrong with you?
What's wrong, General Briscola? Let's go!
We're here to take out some traitors,
so let's stomp them already!
All right!
I heard you loud and clear, Master!
Let's start out with
a Gorilla Punch Punch!
Just for you, Master!
All right.
Looks like Master's given the order.
Gazelle Man! Difugo!
It's time to join the fight!
You see that, Master?
I'm working hard!
Why are all the dipters trying to kill us?
I don't know, man!
Just run away!
We're coming for you, Kaido!
Let's do this!
Everyone follow me!
Gifters, lend me your strength!
Let's fight for our wonderful
master with all we've got!
You're the best!
Thank you, guys!
Oh, Christ!
He's all bloated!
I told you he was dead.
And I told you to shut up!
You're not helping at all!
What do we do?
Captain can help if you were here, but...
Stop fighting.
We need to clear his lungs.
One, two, three!
Booviceye.
Well, if he wasn't dead, you
might have just killed him.
He's rubber, he'll be fine.
Well, I hope he will at least.
Okay.
It's not okay!
Got it, that rubber's burnt.
Captain, help us!
He missed you! He missed you!
But like kites, we rise
highest against the wind!
Minpo, great kite!
Excellent!
Now if I can just find a place to land...
That was awful...
We escaped from that
horrible place, but...
What caused...
What happened to the others? Do you...
Do you think they could still be alive?
Kiku...
Kine-man!
Everyone!
Conney!
I think you mean father,
don't you, Yamato?
I'm here to finally cut ties with you!
Hmm.
Are you sure about that, son?
Don't make me laugh.
You have nothing without me.
Straw Hat is sunk into the sea.
Odin's son suffered the same fate.
If you have the will to fight,
you should have protected
them while you had the chance.
You've got it wrong.
I don't need to protect them.
They're both much stronger than you think.
I fight beside them as equals
and what happens after that?
You think you're gonna break
free of this country of me!
Luffy will show me the world you've
kept from me, but before I leave here.
I'm kicking you out of
this country understand
I won't be going anywhere.
The land of water is extraordinary.
There's no place like it.
You can't defeat me, and I'll never leave.
So stay with me, and become
the Shogun of this country!
I told you no!
And I know I won't be
the one to defeat you.
That's Luffy!
Because he's the man Kozuki
Oden was waiting for!
He'll return, stronger than ever!
All I have to do is
keep you busy till then!
Don't expect me to go easy on you, Yamato!
No mercy!